Later, if you want to go to
a concert and want your eye makeup to be super on
Flicker, I want to show you
how to make
thick eyebrows like mine. Here, I
want to use the three-in-one browser from
Maker. I use the gray brown color.
It already has a spoolie. It already has an
eyebrow pencil. It also has Bramasta. First,
you just comb your eyebrows
according to the shape you want. I
usually just follow the shape of my eyebrows.
Even though the shape of the eyebrows
is triangular like this, it's
really easy to make hair strokes. I
usually start from the middle here and
then I just make a line
backwards but it doesn't have to be too thick
so it doesn't block. If it's him, we
just draw a line for the upper eyebrows
from the middle to the back and just fill
in the empty part. You just have to do it. On the
front side, so it doesn't
block, use the mask brand a little bit. Just
go to the counselor for the eyebrows. They
're still super neat even though my eyebrows are thick
because I tried it too.